So friends, welcome to the final match
on the Hindi channel. Today we will talk about such
stocks which have become close to their item level and
can give very good profits in that picture. So
friends, let's start. The name of the first stock is
Cyber ​​Attack. In this forum,
Bijli Yes Secure has reached and
once it crosses the blue line, then a very
good profit can be seen. You
can pull it above 90687 and
add it to your stock. The name of the stock
is Punjab Chemical. It has also reached its all-time
high and once it
crosses the blue line, means if it crosses above 731 level, then it can give a
very good property.
Kumar can give you a very good profit for the long term.
This is a stop child for you,
you can also add it to your stock. Friends, the
stock to be traded is Birla Software. It has
reached its all-time high and once
it crosses the blue line
including 200 45, then
it can give very good returns and can
go close to the all-time high. This top
image is above 205.  There is Mamta to take it and
add juice to this also on your voice, this
is Yagnik of becoming a spectator in the soil and in this,
recently after crossing his 21 years, he has
started going there with his passport,
this topic is very good and you can send this to
your voice mail, it is
very good for the long term, it is going to give,
fold it here and keep it, when have you done it, you can make ghee
and
earn the definition of, friends, to
watch such videos, please subscribe to my channel
and if you want to ask anything, then like and comment and
thank you for watching the video till the end.